mattressfirm.com 2018-06-03

# Privacy Policy

Last updated: June 16, 2016

Mattress Firm, Inc. (“Mattress Firm,” “we,” “us” and “our”) is committed to making your search for the perfect mattress and a great night sleep as pleasurable and easy as possible. Maintaining your privacy is part of that commitment. As such, this Privacy Policy describes the types of personal and non-personal information we collect on Mattressfirm.com (the “Site”), how we use such information and to whom and under what circumstances we may disclose it. By using the Site, you agree to the collection, use and disclosure of your personally identifiable information as described in this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Site.

Rest Easy: What do we collect?

**Personal Information:**  
Personal information is information that specifically identifies an individual, such as a customer’s name, address, telephone number, e–mail address, credit card or other account number, and information about that individual’s activities when directly linked to that person, such as information about his or her purchases. Personal information also includes demographic information, such as date of birth, gender, geographic area and preferences when such information is linked to other personal information that identifies you. We only collect personal information from you when you: 1) register on the Site and create an account, including any account created using already established social networking accounts such as Facebook or Twitter; 2) complete a survey; 3) sign up for our e-mail list or newsletter; 4) share content from the Site with your friends; 5) contact us by e-mail or by using the chat feature for any reason; or 6) order products and services. 

The Site is a general audience site not directed to children less than 18 years of age and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 18 years of age.

**Non-personal Information:**  
As part of the standard operation of the Site, we may collect certain non-personal information from you, including, but not limited to your Internet IP address, browser type, domain name, operating system, and referring website addresses. In addition, we may collect information about your browsing behavior, such as the date and time you visit the Site, the areas or pages of the Site that you visit, the amount of time you spend viewing the Site, the number of times you return to the Site. This data helps us understand trends and customer needs so that we can better consider new products and services and tailor existing products and services to customer desires. This allows us to make your shopping experience beneficial. 

**Rest Easy: How do we collect your information?**

**Clickstream Data**  
Clickstream data is a record of your activity on the Internet. This data is recorded whenever you click anywhere in a webpage or application and is used for the purposes of collecting, analyzing and reporting data about how you use the Site. This method of data collection is used to capture non-personal information.

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a small text file that may be stored on the hard drive of your computer when you access the Site. A "session cookie" expires immediately when you end your session (i.e., close your browser). A "persistent cookie" stores information on the hard drive so when you end your session and return to the same website at a later date, the cookie information is still available. When you visit our website, we may use both a session and a persistent cookie. These cookies may contain information (such as a unique user ID) that is used to track your usage of our website and in some cases, your e-mail address. Your e-mail address is only saved in this cookie if you register with us. 

If you register with us, this cookie allows us to recognize you when you return to our website and provides you with access to your account information. If you save your information with or order from us, we may also use cookies to monitor and maintain information about your use of our website. 

If you have not saved your information with or ordered from us, we may monitor and maintain information about your use of our website in a manner that does not identify you. We may use cookies to collect the non-personal information described above in order to 1) provide you with customized content and advertising; 2) monitor Site usage; and 3) conduct research to improve our content and services. You are free to decline cookies, but by doing so, you may not be able to use certain features on the Site or take full advantage of all our offerings. Check the “Help” menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences.  

**Pixel Tags**  
A pixel tag (also known as a web beacon) is a small string of code that represents a clear graphic image and is used in conjunction with a cookie. A pixel tag allows us to capture certain additional types of information about a visitor's actions on a web site, such as a visitor's cookie number, the time, date, duration and number of page views, a description of the page where the tag is placed and details about any items that were purchased. Pixel tags help us analyze our customers' online behavior and measure the effectiveness of our website and our advertising. We work with service providers that help us track, collect and analyze this information. 

Rest Easy: How do we use it?

We may share your personal information with members of the Mattress Firm family of businesses to provide you with products or services that you have requested, to provide you with marketing communications regarding products, services, surveys, and promotions and for any other purpose described in this Privacy Policy. We may also share your personal information with service providers and other third parties that need access to your personal information to provide us with operational or other support services, such as payment processors, shipping agents, product fulfillment vendors and fraud prevention service providers, or for marketing research analytics. These third parties must agree to appropriate restrictions on the disclosure and use of your information. Unless otherwise disclosed to you, these third parties are prohibited from using your personal information for their own marketing purposes. We do not rent or sell your personal information to marketers outside the Mattress Firm family of businesses, unless indicated in this Privacy Policy or you otherwise authorize us to do so. We may also use your personal and non-personal information collected for the following purposes: 1) to fulfill your requests for products and services; 2) to provide you with targeted offers and advertising; 3) to contact you with information and promotional materials and offers from Mattress Firm, as well as from our subsidiaries, affiliates, marketing partners, advertisers and other third parties; 4) to contact you if there is a problem with your order; 5) to ask you to review your in-store experience; 6) to review Site usage and operations; 7) to conduct marketing research and/or analysis in order to optimize our search engine marketing strategies; and (8) to guard against fraud, we may on occasion, verify and/or supplement your personal information with information from third party sources. 

In addition, we reserve the right to further use or disclose any information without notice or consent to the following entities for the following purposes: 1) to our employees, independent contractors, subsidiaries, affiliates, consultant, business associates, service providers and suppliers, if the disclosure will enable any of these entities to perform a business, professional or technical support function for us; 2) to our employees, independent contractors, service providers and suppliers, to fulfill a product or service request; 3) as necessary if we believe that there has been a violation of the Site Terms of Use or of our rights or the rights of any third party; 4) to respond to judicial process and provide information to law enforcement agencies or in connection with an investigation on matters related to public safety, as permitted by law, or otherwise as required by law; 5) to conduct investigations of consumer complaints or fraud; and 6) as provided for under the “Unforeseen Circumstances” section below.

Rest Easy: How secure is our site?

Mattress Firm, Inc. takes your security seriously. We have taken certain physical, electronic, contractual and managerial steps to safeguard and secure the information we collect from Site visitors. We have limited access to private and confidential data to those employees with a specific need to retrieve this information. To maintain this highest level of security, we do not store private information on the Site. We do not direct the Site to, nor do we knowingly collect, any personal information from children under the age of eighteen. 

All of your information is encrypted before it is transmitted across the Internet. Additionally, the information you provide when you place an order is encrypted (or coded) using a secure server for maximum security. This coding makes it extremely difficult for anyone to reach your information as it moves through our ordering system. 

Most of the pages on our site provide information about Mattress Firm and our products and do not contain secure information or ask for your personal information. We make this information available freely and there's no reason for these pages to be secure. The pages that we make secure are the "Checkout area" and pages on which you actually make a purchase, manage your account, or check your order status. For example, the entire checkout process, from introduction to final confirmation, is completely secure. When confirming an order, the confirmation page will display your shipping address, billing address, and payment method (e.g. credit card). Your credit card number will not be displayed on this page. If you are logged into your account, your profile page will display the last four digits of the credit card you have on file. It will not display your full credit card number. You may add new credit card information or delete current credit card information but you will not be able to edit any of your credit card information. 

When you create an account on our site, we will store some of your personal information. This will include your name, login information (except passwords), shipping address, billing address, order information, wish list information, and payment settings. If you log in using a social media site such as Facebook, we will capture and store that login information as well. 

To check the security of your computer, look for a padlock to either the left or right of the URL. If you see a closed padlock, then the encryption technology is active and the server is secure. You can also check by looking at the URL line of your browser. When you access a secure server, the initial characters of the site address will be "https." 

You also have an obligation to safeguard your own personal information. If you set up an account on our site, it is your responsibility to keep your password and profile information confidential. We recommend using a complex password with unique number, letters and special characters. If you are sharing a computer, you should always log out before leaving a site to protect access to your information from subsequent users. If your password has been compromised for any reason, you should immediately change your password. 

**Third-Party Websites**  
The Site may contain links to third-party websites, which may have privacy policies that differ from our own. We are not responsible for the activities and practices that take place on these sites. Accordingly, we recommend that you review the privacy policy posted on any site that you may access through our Site. 

**Unforeseen Circumstances**  
As we continue to develop our business, we or our affiliates may sell or buy other businesses or entities. In such transactions, personal information may be one of the transferred business assets. Also, in the event that Mattress Firm, Inc. or substantially all of its assets are acquired, your personal information may be one of the transferred assets. 

**Third Party Advertising Partners**  
We use third-party service providers to serve advertisements (banners or links) on our behalf across the Internet. 

These advertising service providers may collect non-identifiable information about your visits to our website, and your interactions with our products and services. Such non-identifiable information does not include your name, address, e-mail address or other personal information. The information is collected through the use of cookies and pixel tags. 

In addition to the information about your visits to our website, our service providers may also use the information about your visits to other websites to target advertisements for products and services available from Mattress Firm.

Currently, we use third party-placed tracking pixels and cookies from the following advertising delivery partners: TruEffect, Amazon and Google. In the future we may partner with other companies to provide interest-based advertising, both on and off the Site. If this occurs, Mattress Firm provides you with an opportunity to opt out when these advertisements are served. You may manage your third-party advertising preferences by clicking on the links below: 

  * [I would like to opt OUT of Google Analytics Display Advertising.](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/)

If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices for not having this information used by third-party service providers, please visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>

**Facebook Custom Audience Ads**  
We may display interest-based ads to you when you are using Facebook through a tool offered by Facebook called the Custom Audience Tool. This tool allows us to personalize our ads based on your shopping experience with us. We do not share any of your personal information, including your shopping history, with Facebook. The tool lets Mattress Firm convert your e-mail address to a unique number that Facebook uses to match to unique numbers Facebook generates from e-mail addresses of its users.

**Google Custom Match Ads**  
We may display interest-based ads to you when you are using Google through a tool offered by Google called the Custom Match Program. This tool allows us to personalize our ads based on your shopping experience with us. We do not share any of your personal information with Google. The tool lets Mattress Firm convert your e-mail address to a unique number that Google uses to match to unique numbers Google generates from e-mail addresses of its users.

**E-mail Marketing**  
If you are opted in to receive marketing e-mails from us and wish to unsubscribe, you can do so by clicking on the Unsubscribe hyperlink at the bottom of the marketing e-mail you receive. We will note in our database that you have elected to opt out of future e-mails from our company. Your record will still remain in our database but you will not receive any future mailings unless we manually opt you back in. 

You may also choose to opt out of e-mails by sending an e-mail to us at customerservice@mattressfirm.com. If you choose to opt out with this method, please be sure to include the e-mail address that you would like us to unsubscribe.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**  
We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. When we do, we will post the change(s) on the Site. If we change our Privacy Policy in a material way, we will provide appropriate online notice to you. 

If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [customerservice@mattressfirm.com](mailto:customerservice@mattressfirm.com).
